viralsweep.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - ViralSweep

This web page represents a legal document that serves as our Privacy Policy and it governs the privacy terms of our Website. Our Privacy Policy is considered part of and subject to our Legal Terms. Any terms not defined herein have the same meaning as defined elsewhere in our Legal Terms. The last update to our Privacy Policy was posted on November 12, 2014.

## Your Privacy

ViralSweep follows all legal requirements to protect your privacy. Our Privacy Policy is a legal statement that explains how we may collect information from you, how we may share your information, and how you can limit our sharing of your information. You will see terms in our Privacy Policy that are capitalized. These terms have meanings as described in the Definitions section below.

## Definitions

"Non Personal Information" is information that is not personally identifiable to you and that we automatically collect when you access our Website with a web browser.

"Personally Identifiable Information" is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained in order for us to provide you with our Website. Personally Identifiable Information may include information such as your company information, your name, email address, and other related information that you provide to us or that we obtain about you.

## Information We Collect

Generally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to ViralSweep when using our Website. However, we also collect information from Contestants on your behalf that may be classified under local, state, federal, and international laws as Personally Identifiable Information.

As a Visitor, you can browse our Website to find out more about ViralSweep and the Service we offer. You are not required to provide us with any Personally Identifiable Information as a Visitor.

However, if you register as a Member to use our Service, you must provide Personally Identifiable Information to ViralSweep in order for us to provide you with certain features of our Website. As a Member, we collect your Personally Identifiable Information in the following ways:

**At Member Registration**  
When you register for membership, we collect your company name, your name and email address.

**Our Service**  
Our Service allows for the collection of data from Contestants on your behalf. We will not share Contest data with anyone else but you. We never sell, trade, or rent users personal identification information to others. However, our Privacy Policy is not a guarantee of your legal right to collect information from Contestants; you are solely responsible for insuring that you follow applicable privacy laws with regards to Contest data.

**Online Forms**  
There may be online forms used in our Website. The information you enter into these online forms may contain Personally Identifiable Information.

## Computer Information Collected

ViralSweep automatically collects certain computer information by the interaction of a mobile phone or web browser with our Website. Such information is typically considered Non Personal Information. ViralSweep also collects and uses the following web-based information:

**Cookies**  
Our Website uses “Cookies” to identify the areas of our Website that you have visited. A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser. We use Cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our Website. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access functionality on our Website correctly or at all. We never place Personally Identifiable Information in Cookies.

**Web Beacons**  
We may also use a technology called Web Beacons, to collect general information about your use of our Website and your use of special promotions or newsletters. The information we collect by Web Beacons allows us to statistically monitor the number of people that open our emails. Our Web Beacons are not used to track your activity outside of our Website. We do not link Non Personal Information from Web Beacons to Personally Identifiable Information without your permission.

**Automatic Information**  
We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the name of the Website from which you entered our Website, if any, as well as the name of the website to which you’re headed when you leave our Website. This information also includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system. We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website.

## How We Use Your Information

ViralSweep uses the information we receive from you as follows:

**Providing our Service**  
In order use our Service, you will have to expose some Personally Identifiable Information. Your Contestants will also likely be exposing Personally Identifiable Information as part of registering for your Contests. Again, we do not share your Contest data with anyone but you, and we will never contact your Contestants.

**Communication and Email Alerts**  
When ViralSweep communicates with you about our Website, we will use the email address you provided when registering as a Member. We may also send you service alerts regarding your use of our Website. Finally, we may also send you emails with promotional information about ViralSweep, unless you have opted out of receiving such information. You can change contact preferences at any time through your account. While you can opt-out of promotional messages, you cannot opt-out of receiving service alerts.

**Customizing Our Website and Mobile Application**  
ViralSweep may use the Personally Identifiable information you provide to us along with any computer information we receive to customize our Website.

**Sharing Information with Affiliates and Other Third Parties**  
ViralSweep does not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your Personally Identifiable Information or your Contest data to third parties other than as specified in our Legal Terms. However, we may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to affiliates that provide services to ViralSweep with regards to our Website (i.e. payment processors, hosting companies, etc.). Such affiliates will only receive information necessary to provide the respective services and will be bound by confidentiality agreements limiting the use of such information.

**Legally Required Releases of Information**  
ViralSweep may be legally required to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information as well as your Contest data, if such disclosure is (a) required by subpoena, law, or other legal process; (b) necessary to assist law enforcement officials or government enforcement agencies; (c) necessary to investigate violations of or otherwise enforce our Legal Terms; (d) necessary to protect us from legal action or claims from third parties including you and/or other Members; and/or (e) necessary to protect the legal rights, personal/real property, or personal safety of ViralSweep, our Users, employees, and affiliates.

**Disclosures to Successors**  
If ViralSweep is acquired or merges, in whole or in part, with another business that would become responsible for providing the Website to you, we retain the right to transfer your Personally Identifiable Information as well as your Contest data to the new business. The new business would retain the right to use your Personally Identifiable Information according to the terms of this Privacy Policy as well as to any changes to this Privacy Policy as instituted by the new business.

## "Do Not Track/Follow" Settings

In compliance with applicable laws, ViralSweep wants you to know that our Website does not currently honor “do not track” or “do not follow” settings as your web browser may allow, nor do we have any liability for not doing so. If we change our policy in the future, it will be reflected here in an update to our Privacy Policy.

## Changing Your Information

You may change your Personally Identifiable Information at any time using the Account & Settings Tab on our Website.

## Protecting Your Child’s Privacy

Our Website is not designed for use by a Child. You acknowledge that we cannot accurately verify the age of our Users nor do we have any liability to do so. If you are parent or legal guardian who suspects their Child is attempting to use our Website, please contact us immediately to remove your Child’s information. We will ask you to provide identification to confirm that you are indeed the Child’s parent or legal guardian. If you are a Child, please don’t access or use our Website.

## Protecting the Privacy Rights of Others

If you are a Contestant participating in a Contest operated by one of our Members and you have a privacy question regarding the Contest, please contact the Member who is operating the Contest. We do not do anything with your information other than provide it to the Member whose Contest you entered.

## Links to Other Websites

Our Website may contain links to other websites. You agree that ViralSweep has no control over such websites and that such websites are NOT subject to this Privacy Policy. These websites may have their own privacy policies and other legal documents. It is your sole responsibility to verify the privacy policies and other legal documents of such websites to see how they treat your personal information. You acknowledge that your use and access of these websites is solely at your own risk.

## Our Email Policy

ViralSweep and our affiliates fully comply with laws regarding SPAM. You can always opt out of receipt of further email correspondence from ViralSweep and/or our affiliates. We agree that we will not sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third-party without your permission.

## Our Security Policy

ViralSweep has constructed our Website using industry standard encryption and authentication tools to protect your Personally Identifiable Information. When we collect your Personally Identifiable Information through our Website, we encrypt this information and attempt to prevent unauthorized access to it by using industry standard technologies, such as encryption routers and firewalls. Unfortunately, due to the nature of the Internet, we cannot completely guarantee that your Personally Identifiable Information is completely protected. We strongly urge you to protect any password you may have for our Website and to not share it with anyone. You should always log out of our Website when not in use, especially if you are sharing a computer or mobile device with someone else or are using a public computer.

## Safe Harbor and International Users

For European Union and Swiss Residents: providing us with your Personal Information means you are consenting to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers located in the United States. ViralSweep adheres to the safe harbor framework regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information collected.

## Payment Sources

You may be required to provide a payment source for using our Service. You acknowledge that we don’t store your payment source information directly on our servers and use third-party billing providers to process your payment source. We work with such providers to insure your payment source information is encrypted and protected. However, you understand and agree that we do not control nor can we be liable for the acts of third parties. If you see what you believe to be fraudulent transactions regarding our Website, please contact us immediately. We will make reasonable efforts to work with you and authorities to help resolve such issues.

## Privacy Policy Updates

ViralSweep reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. You should review this Privacy Policy frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. We will also change the "Last Updated" date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies.

## Questions About Our Privacy Practices or This Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about our Privacy Practices or this Policy, please contact us by using our Contact Us form or by emailing us at help[at]viralsweep[dot]com
